Justice will be served.
Gunfight at Rio Bravo is a western, action film directed by Joe Cornet.
When mysterious Russian gunslinger Ivan Turchin rides into a small Texas town, he
runs afoul of a bloodthirsty outlaw gang known as The Hellhounds.
Outmanned and outgunned, the town must put their trust in Turchin to
protect them from annihilation at the hands of the bandits.
The gunslinger finds allies in the form of Marshal Austin Carter and Sheriff Vernon Kelly, and
together the three must make a desperate stand against impossible and violent odds.
Ivan Turchin, played by Alexander Nevsky.
Marshall Austin Carter, played by Olivier Gruner.
Sheriff Vernon Kelly, played by Joe Cornet.
Ethan Crawley, played by Matthias Hues.
Nora Miller, played by Natalie Denise Sperl.
Jenny Gray, played by Kerry Goodwin.
Gunfight at Rio Bravo is an American action western film, released in 2023.
The tone is dark.